Rob: Hey, Alan.
Would you like to come to the match with me on Sunday?
It’s Norwich against Chelsea, and I have two tickets.
Alan: Wow!
What time’s the match?
Rob: It’s at four o’clock.
Alan: Yeah, I’d love to. Thanks.
Rob: Would you like to meet for lunch first?
Alan: Sorry, I can’t.
It’s my mum’s birthday,
and I need to have lunch with her.
But I can meet you there.
Rob: Great.
Let’s meet at half past three at the entrance to the Tube station.
Alan: Fine. See you there.
Alan: They are playing really badly.
I hope the second half is better.
Rob: Me, too. I know they can win.
Would you like a burger?
Alan: No, thanks. I’m not very hungry.
Rob: How about a coffee?
Alan: Yeah, great.
Rob: Um, a burger and a water, please.
Alan: And I’d like a coffee.
Barman: Milk and sugar?
Alan: Yes, please.